[Music]
life is full of unlimited joys today we
have unlimited dog time plans unlimited
data unlimited food what if you had
unlimited wishes too sorry that's just a
fantasy if you had only one wish we know
you'd wish for unlimited happiness and
health for your loved ones so when your
love and care knows no limit then why
should your health insurance care
unlimited with the health infinity plan
by Petrucelli aren't strictly insurance
with unlimited sum insured for you and
your family during hospitalization if
your medical growth starts climbing you
will never have to worry if your policy
will cover it before the summit short
runs out because help infinity gives you
unlimited coverage with unlimited sum in
short not only that you will get
wellness discounts every time you renew
your policy you get rode ambulance cover
of 5,000 per hospitalization your plan
now covers boarding expenses of up to
50,000 per day as we understand your
need for comfort and tranquility for
recuperation and westphall experience
there won't be any sub limits on
inpatient hospitalization treatment
[Music]
pre-existing diseases will be covered
after 36 months from a first health
policy
[Music]
get preventive health checkups Donna at
the end of every three consecutive
policy yet you get various full payment
options to choose from
you get 60 days free and 90 days first
hospitalization cover we will also cover
day care procedures there are no medical
tests on frequency for up to the age of
45 availing contacts benefit under
Section a TD under ID Act
so purchase your very own but your
journey ons health infinitely plan with
unlimited cover and live worryfree
[Music]
you